

Software Developer

eriamiatoeefe11@gmail.com +2348115737426 Abuja, Nigeria

Date / Place of birth January 12th / Benin City

Nationality Nigerian

Efe Eriamiatoe

Profile

I am a dental surgeon with 3 years experience working in that field and for the past two years I have diversified into tech especially web development. I Interned at Grokkinglabs Abuja where I was able to hone my frontend and backend skills to become the reliable full stack developer I am today.

Employment History

Intern at Grokkinglabs, Abuja

12/2021-07/2022

Worked on and developed a blog using Django. Also currently working on a Django e-commerce website soon to be deployed. Currently working on a social media Django application

Dental surgeon at Ivory dental care, Abuja

12/2021-06/2022

Performed numerous dental surgical procedures including:

Root canal treatment

Trans and intra alveolar exodontia

Temporary and permanent fillings

Crown preparation and delivery

Teeth whitening and scaling and polishing

Denture design and fabrication

Implant surgery

Education

Advanced Django web development, Udemy, Abuja

05/2022-09/2022

Really took my Django and react skills to an advanced level

Responsive web design, FreeCodeCamp, Abuja

12/2021-02/2022

Links

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/eriamiatoe-efe
My portfolio:

https://efosblack.github.io/my_portfolio/

Diango blog project:

http://efeblogapp.herokuapp.com/

Django chat web app:

https://github.com/efosblack/my_chat

Skills

ITML/CSS/JavaScript	4/5		
Python	5/5		
Django React PostgressSQL Ability to Work in a Team Fast Learner	4/5 5/5		
		Critical thinking and problem solving	5/5
		Communication Skills	5/5

Hobbies

Football, swimming, videogames, card magic, writing

Graduated with excellent grades on all my projects in html and css

CS50 introduction to computer science, EDX, Abuja

01/2021-04/2022

Mastered the basis of computer science and got great grades on all my projects

Python for everybody, EDX, Abuja

12/2021-06/2022

Excelled in all my assignments and projects using python

Bachelor of dental surgery, University of Benin, Benin City

11/2012-09/2021

Graduated with high honours in the field of dental surgery

Personal projects

My Portfolio, Abuja

08/2022-09/2022

Using HTML/CSS, JavaScript and React I built my portfolio website and hosted it on GitHub.io

Django blog app, Abuja

06/2022-07/2022

I created a blog application using python-Django web framework for the backend and HTML/CSS with JavaScript for the frontend and hosted it on heroku

Django chat app, Abuja

12/2021-01/2022

I created a simple web chat room using python-Django for backend and HTML/CSS for front end and hosted it on GitHub

Internships

Software engineer intern at Grokkinglabs, Abuja

12/2021-Present

Worked on a Django blog application

Assisted in various frontend development projects with React and JavaScript

Currently working on an e-commerce website using Django and react

References

Gabriel Alexander Stephen from DevOps and Realibility engineer at openMined Stephen@openmined.org +234803 743 1441

Languages

English Native speaker